<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Life So Far // Days Ahead</title>
    <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Life So Far // Days Ahead</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Ask for Feedback</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/dont-ask-for-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/dont-ask-for-feedback/</guid>
      <description>You’re already awesome</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five tips for effective team members</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/effective-team-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/effective-team-members/</guid>
      <description>Do not impede other&amp;rsquo;s work The essential trait of a good teammate is someone who does not impede others work. This applies in both vertical and horizontal relationships. If you are a manager, and your Director is going to implement a process that will impede your team, is it your absolute obligation to speak up against such a thing. If your coworkers is working on a project, you must not impede their progress in any way, unless their actions directly impact you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move The Needle</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/moving-the-needle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/moving-the-needle/</guid>
      <description>Every morning after rolling out of bed, I ask myself the same question: “How can I move the needle today?” I find myself asking the same question right before falling asleep, too. Now that I’m going into the office, I ask myself this question walking along the chain fenced pathway from the parking lot. It’s stuck in my head and always repeating.
Moving the needle means making a NOTICEABLE impact to your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three tips on finding fulfillment in your career</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/finding-fulfillment-in-your-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/finding-fulfillment-in-your-career/</guid>
      <description>I never knew what I wanted to do when I grew up – and then I grew up.
Until I was about 27 years old - I studied, graduated, studied some more, got a degree, then another… my life was a continuous stream of achievement and reorientation, always reaching for the next accolade. Regardless of these achievements, the truly best moments of my life up to that point were those when I was either DJing a party or going to music festivals with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I made my resume in LaTeX (&#43; free template)</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/why-i-made-my-resume-in-latex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/why-i-made-my-resume-in-latex/</guid>
      <description>I’ve received a few job offers in my life and even more rejection letters. One thing that has always followed me along the way is my resume. The resume is a standard requirement during most application processes because it sums you up into one easy to digest page. For this reason alone, you must do everything you can to make it easy to read and effectively communicate the right information about who you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Something</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/make-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/make-something/</guid>
      <description>I often bake desserts for friends and family. It’s not a regular occurrence, but it always results in good feelings. Who doesn’t love a chocolate chip cookie? Unfortunately, my budget of high-quality dark chocolate and free time limits this giving, as does the size of my oven and kitchenaid mixer. Usually, the best yields are 10-15 quick sparks of joy and energy from a single batch.
Not bad – 15:1 ratio for a few hours of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Why a blog? At 28, it feels like I&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way, but I know this is only just the beginning. As I write, I hope to capture my ideas and my current mindset, maybe even provide some guidance to those who need it.
As of today, I work for SpaceX on the Dragon Supply Chain Team as a Buyer for mechanisms and mechanical assemblies. Prior to this, I was a Buyer at Volvo Cars USA, as awell as a Buyer and Mechanical Engineer for TRU Simulation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
