<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life So Far // Days Ahead</title>
    <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Life So Far // Days Ahead</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chrisrussell.blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I made my resume in LaTeX (&#43; free template)</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/why-i-made-my-resume-in-latex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/why-i-made-my-resume-in-latex/</guid>
      <description>I’ve received a few job offers in my life and even more rejection letters. One thing that has always followed me along the way is my resume. The resume is a standard requirement during most application processes because it sums you up into one easy to digest page. For this reason alone, you must do everything you can to make it easy to read and effectively communicate the right information about who you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Something</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/make-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/make-something/</guid>
      <description>I often bake desserts for friends and family. It’s not a regular occurrence, but it always results in good feelings. Who doesn’t love a chocolate chip cookie? Unfortunately, my budget of high-quality dark chocolate and free time limits this giving, as does the size of my oven and kitchenaid mixer. Usually, the best yields are 10-15 quick sparks of joy and energy from a single batch.
Not bad – 15:1 ratio for a few hours of work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my site. I&amp;rsquo;ve build this as a platform to express my ideas and hopefully offer some advice. Feel free to reach out to my personal mail here.
Lets begin.
-Chris</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Why a blog? I&amp;rsquo;ve come a long ways in my 28 years as a student and professional. I think by now I might have a few ideas of my own to share and offer perspective from my journey.
As of today, I work for SpaceX on the Dragon Supply Chain Team as a Buyer for mechanisms and mechanical assemblies. Prior to this, I was a Buyer at Volvo Cars USA, as awell as a Buyer and Engineer for TRU Simulation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
