<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>success on Life So Far // Days Ahead</title>
    <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/tags/success/</link>
    <description>Recent content in success on Life So Far // Days Ahead</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chrisrussell.blog/tags/success/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Five tips for effective team members</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/effective-team-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/effective-team-members/</guid>
      <description>Do not impede other&amp;rsquo;s work Good teammates do not impede other&amp;rsquo;s work. This applies in both vertical and horizontal relationships. If your Manager plans to implement a process that will impede your team, is it your absolute obligation to speak up. If your coworker is working on a project, you must not impede their progress in any way, unless their actions directly impact you.
Speak Up Authenticity is perishable. From the moment you feel it in your gut, the countdown begins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Ask for Feedback</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/dont-ask-for-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/dont-ask-for-feedback/</guid>
      <description>Don’t Ask for Feedback You’re already awesome.
You don&amp;rsquo;t need anyone to verify this.
Good teammates will tell you what to work on.
They’re called blind spots for a reason.
Ask specific questions if you have them.
Let people rip into your work. Don’t get defensive. Thank them profusely.
Let your guard down.
Listen to their words, hear what they say, then do what you want – others will do the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move The Needle</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/moving-the-needle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/moving-the-needle/</guid>
      <description>Every morning after rolling out of bed, I ask myself the same question: “How can I move the needle today?” I find myself asking the same question right before falling asleep, too. Now that I’m going into the office, I ask myself this question walking along the chain fenced pathway from the parking lot. It’s stuck in my head and always repeating.
Moving the needle means making a NOTICEABLE impact to your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three tips on finding fulfillment in your career</title>
      <link>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/finding-fulfillment-in-your-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chrisrussell.blog/posts/finding-fulfillment-in-your-career/</guid>
      <description>I never knew what I wanted to do when I grew up – and then I grew up.
Until I was about 27 years old - I studied, graduated, studied some more, got a degree, then another… my life was a continuous stream of achievement and reorientation, always reaching for the next accolade. Regardless of these achievements, the truly best moments of my life up to that point were those when I was either DJing a party or going to music festivals with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
